kissthisguy.com 2019-06-20

# KissThisGuy.com Privacy Notice

## Latest Misheard Stories

### Artist: Statler Brothers

### Song: Eve

**The Story:** Don't eat the fruit in the garden, Eden,, It wasn't in God's natural plan., You were only a rib,, And look at what you did,, To Adam, the father of Man.

Continue Reading...

### Artist: Queens of the Stone Age

### Song: You Can't Quit Me Baby

**The Story:** You smell like goat, I'll see you in hell

Continue Reading...

### Artist: Starship

### Song: Sarah

**The Story:** All the b***h had said, all been washed in black

Continue Reading...

### Artist: Iron Maiden

### Song: The Prisoner

**The Story:** And my blunt is my ho now

Continue Reading...

### Artist: Pearl Jam

### Song: Jeremy

**The Story:** At home, drawing pictures, Of mounds of tots, With ham on top

Continue Reading...

## Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

### The Information We Collect: The submission process.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on www.kissthisguy.com and affiliated sites. The submission engine lets you submit info on your name, email address, age of mishearance, and other OPTIONAL details. 

### The Way We Use Submission Information: 

We use the information you optionally provide about yourself only to offer it for re-display to other viewers and members, should your submission be accepted and published. If you do not want to share this information with the world, do not fill in form fields requesting this information. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not shared with third-parties without your consent. 

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

Members can access their personally identifiable information by logging into their personal profile [add hyperlink here] and entering your ID and password as required. 

The continuation of the policy below address additional personally identifiable information and site usage 

### Personal Information

  * **Viewers without an Account.** You can view, vote and send in corrections or comments without an account on KissThisGuy.
  * **Members with Personal Accounts.** Registered members on KissThisGuy can perform other activities such as submitting lyrics and content, create personal favorites lists, create my lyrics lists and communicate with the site on a priority basis. Members, in the near future, may also be able to obtain restricted editing privileges and post comments directly to related content. We ask for some personal information when you create a KissThisGuy profile/account , including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.
  * **Usage Information.** We may record information about your usage, such as when you use KissThisGuy.com, the favorites you compile, and the frequency and size of data upload or transfers, as well as information you provide in your personal profile. If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account.
  * **Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information, text, video or sound you voluntarily disclose online (in messages and chat areas, within your personal profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your personal information, such as your email address will remain private. 

### Uses

  * If you submit personally identifiable information to KissThisGuy or our affiliated sites, we may use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality we have available currently or may develop in the future.
  * Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other viewers and members when you submit lyrics, videos or sound clips send messages to other members of KissThisGuy.com [some of the aforementioned features are in development status] . Any submission [text, video, sound et cetera] to KissThisGuy may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major KissThisGuy site changes or for customer service purposes). 
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of KissThisGuy or affiliated site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit KissThisGuy and affiliated sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions and contests or game activity. 

### Your Choices

  * You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information to KissThisGuy or affiliated sites, in which case you can still view our content and explore (surf) the site(s), but KissThisGuy and affiliates may not be able to provide certain services or features to you. 
  * You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your Profile. 

### Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

KissThisGuy and affiliated sites allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our available ad space. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the KissThisGuy and affiliated sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

KissThisGuy and affiliated sites do not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks KissThisGuy and affiliated sites to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 35-64 who have viewed certain content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of KissThisGuy or affiliated sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. KissThisGuy�s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
